Can I take a few pictures?
ちょっといっぱい撮っていい?
With my boyfriend, yeah.
彼氏とさ、 うん
Have you ever left a hedge while taking pictures like this?
あの、こういう撮りながら、 ヘッジ残したことある?
Do you want to be photographed?
撮られたことする?
No, because I get photographed a lot.
いや、撮られること多いからさ
Why such a story?
なんでそんなストーリーの?
I'm not doing anything anymore.
もう、なんと、何もしてない
Just taking pictures?
写真撮ってるだけで?
Take a photo,
写真撮りさ、
I want to see the back too.
後 ろも見たいな
Do you know where the photo was taken?
どこ撮られてるかわかる?
yeah?
ん?
Don't you know?
わかんない?
Time, yeah.
時間とかさ、 うん
Have you ever been read aloud?
読説とかされたことないの?
do not have.
ない
It's not just that you don't notice.
気づかないだけではないんだ
That's a mini-skirtson.
それミニスカーソンだ
But it's a little see-through under the ribbon.
でもちょっと透けてんだね、リバンの下のところ
There's a sense of transparency.
そういう、なんか透け感があるの
Yeah.
うん
Were you surprised?
びっくりした?
Yeah.
うん
Underwear with underwear?
下着で下着?
Yeah.
うん
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
It was delicious.
かずかったよ
Is the photo taken in a bad way?
撮られ方が悪いかな?
Let's take a proper picture.
ちゃんと撮っておいておこう
different.
違う
different?
違う?
Yeah.
うん
Still fake?
フェイクがいまだ?
Well, there's no correct answer.
ま、正解なし
No fakes?
フェイクがいない?
Yeah.
うん
It's super smooth.
超すべすべだね
Did you hide it?
隠しちゃった?
Yeah.
うん
What's going on inside?
中がどうなってんの?
Is it okay to look inside?
中見ていいんでしょう?
Yeah.
うん
You said it was fine earlier.
いいって言ってたじゃん、さっき
Isn't it okay?
いいんでしょう?
I'm kind of curious about that.
なんか気になるんだよね
Your skin is pure white, huh?
肌真っ白だね、あの
white.
白い
It's really white.
ほんとすごい白い
That's it.
あのさ
Yeah.
うん
That's right, Masaki.
そうだよ、まさきと
Who is this person?
この人は誰だっけ?
Please wait.
お待ちなさい
They look similar.
似てるね
Are you told?
言われる?
Not at all.
まったく
Are you told?
言われる?
Not told?
言われない?
Yeah.
うん
Are they similar?
似てる?
They don't look alike.
似てない
Just don't say it instead.
ちょっと代わりに言わずで
yeah?
ん?
what?
何?
no doubt.
間違いない
I don't like it.
嫌
What?
何が?
I don't like it.
嫌
picture?
え?
I don't like it, it's normal.
嫌だ、普通に
What?
何が?
I was just telling you to pick up your pen.
筆上げてって言ってただけだよ
Yeah, I don't like it.
うん、嫌だ
After that?
それからなの?
why?
なんで?
I don't like it.
嫌
tell me.
教えて
I don't like it.
嫌
What?
何が?
Then please tell me why you don't like it.
じゃあなんで嫌か言ってくれたらいいよ
I just don't like it.
普通に嫌だ
Do you not like it?
嫌なの?
I just don't like it.
普通に嫌だ
There's nothing wrong with that.
何かとかない
I don't like it.
嫌だ
what?
何?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
Yeah.
うん
What?
何が?
Yeah.
うん
What's wrong?
何がとかないの?
what?
何?
Do you just dislike it?
普通に嫌なの?
Because I don't hate it.
嫌じゃないから
I hated it once.
嫌ったじゃん、一回
That's why it's good.
だからいいじゃん
Oh, hey.
ああ、ちょっと
I don't like it.
嫌
I told you I didn't like it.
嫌なきゃ言ってたじゃん
I said you can take it.
取っていいよって
It doesn't matter where you are.
どこだったらいいんだじゃん
I don't like it anywhere.
どこも嫌
picture?
え?
I don't like it anywhere.
どこも嫌
You said you'd make me look pretty.
綺麗な顔してくれるって言ってたじゃん
I didn't say he would talk to me.
喋 ってくれるとは言ってない
I just touched it when I was in my underwear.
下着さまってたら触れちゃっただけじゃん
da
ダ
Me?
メ なの?
yes.
はい
Then next time,
じゃあ今度、
Turn around once.
一 回向いて
Wake up once and wave to me.
一回起きて、こっちに手を振って
Goo more.
もっとグーって
This one is also aimed at the face.
こっちの方も顔向けで
Is it okay to take off your underwear?
下着取るのいいんでしょ?
Because it's different.
違いになっちゃってるから
It was crap.
くずかったよ
It's already small and has a cute butt.
もう小ぶりで可愛いお尻にしてるね
I've been using this underwear for quite some time.
結構この下着長く使ってるの
More and more.
もっともっと
What should I do?
どうだったらいいんだ?
No way.
やだ
feel?
感じる?
Around here?
この辺?
no.
いや
It was crap.
くずかったよ
Was it crumbling?
くずかったよ?
Your body is so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗だね、体
My body shape hasn't changed since I was in middle school.
中学生くらいからもう変わんない体型
You understand, right?
分かるでしょ?
Clothes size doesn't make any difference, right?
服のサイズでも何も変わらないでしょ?
It's small.
小ぶりな
It's really beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗ほんと
Because I can't see well.
よく見えないから
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Is that not okay?
そっちはダメなの?
Is that good?
そっちは良いのに?
not good.
良くない
not good?
良くない?
That's fine.
いいじゃん
I don't like it.
嫌だよ
Will you give me a prank?
ツンってしてあげる?
No?
ダメ?
Tsun is no good.
ツンはダメ
I was wondering what would happen.
どうなるかなと思って
What do you think?
どうなの?
Can I eat it?
食べしていい?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Maybe nothing will happen.
何も起こらないかもしれないけど
I just want to confirm the result that nothing happens.
何 も起こらないって言うとの結果をちょっと確認したいんだ
But.
けど
Then let's get up.
じゃあ 起きよう
Okay then?
じゃあいい?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
That's not going to happen.
そこは起こらないんだ
It's solid there.
そこは固いんだな
Huh?
あれ?
Isn't it okay?
いいんじゃないの?
Are you putting in effort?
力入ってる?
what?
何?
That's all you said.
それだけで言ってたじゃん
I'll give it to you again for a plus.
プラスでまたあげるからさ
Do you want to enter?
入れたい?
Will it end soon?
すぐ終われる?
It's just a little monkey.
ちょっとさるだけだから
I'm not even upset.
ツンもしてないよ
Look at your fingers.
指見てみて
I don't even have a tsun.
ツンもしてないから
It hurts if I press hard
強く押したら痛いで
Sho?
しょ?
Take a look.
見て みて
Nothing changes.
何も変わらない
You said it was nothing.
何もなんないって言ってたね
Take a look.
ちょっと見てみて
What happened?
どうなった?
Nothing has happened.
何もなってない
I burst out laughing though.
吹き出てきたけど
tickles.
くすぐったい
What do you mean when you say it's blown out?
吹き出てきたって言うのはどういうこと?
tickles.
くすぐったい
Don't hide it.
隠さないでさ
When it stops nearby.
近 くで止まると
How many cups?
何カップ?
3 cups.
3カップ
It's already ticklish.
もうくすぐったい
What should I do?
どうすればいい?
You don't have to do anything.
どうもしなくていいよ
What about this?
こっちは?
They seem to have different sensitivities.
感度違うらしいんだよね
on the right and left.
右と左で
or
や
No, no?
っちゃ ダメ?
It's not ticklish.
くすぐったくないんすよ
It's ticklish.
く すぐったいもん
Where should it be?
どこだったらいい?
Everything tickles.
全部くすぐったい
Are they all ticklish?
全部くすぐったい?
Everything tickles.
全部くすぐったい
You get into that mode.
そういうモードに入っちゃうよね
surely.
確かに
If you think it's ticklish, everything will be ticklish.
くすぐったいって思っちゃうと、全部くすぐったくなっちゃう
Like.
みたい
surely.
確 かに
Is it like this?
こういう感じかな?
surely.
確かに
Isn't this ticklish?
こっちはくすぐったくないの?
surely.
確かに
How tickled was it?
どこまでくすぐったは?
tickles.
くすぐったい
Was it easy?
楽やった?
It's not so ticklish.
こんなにくすぐったくないとか
Quake doesn't tickle, right?
quakeのくすぐったくないでしょ?
tickles.
くすぐったい
picture?
え?
It doesn't tickle, does it?
くすぐったくないでしょ
That's not ticklish.
それはくすぐったくない.
Look.
ほら
It doesn't tickle, does it?
くすぐったくないでしょ
cold.
冷たい
Well, punch.
ええと、パンチ
I want to check because it doesn't tickle me.
くすぐったくないから確認したい
It's not ticklish, you know.
くすぐったくないでしょ、ほら
Hey.
ねえ
Good day.
グッダイ
You're saying it's not good.
グッダイかないなね、と言ってるでしょ
This is how you turn on the power.
電源やるとこうやって
Wow, I'm going to take a lot of sol.
うわぁ、めっちゃゾールを取る
Eh, this is what you put on ice cubes.
え、片氷とかにつくんだよ、これ
Wow, no, I'm really going to take Zoll.
うわぁ、いや、めっちゃゾールを取る
Hey, hey, hey, nothing, nothing, nothing.
ちょ、ちょ、ちょ、なし、なし、なし
The whole body was removed.
全身取り外されたった
TRUE?
本当?
No, no, no, no.
やだ、やだ、やだ、やだ
It really has been removed.
本当に取り外さってるね
I'm really bad at it.
めっちゃ苦手
It's really removed.
本当に取り外さってる
Very painful
めっちゃ苦
hand.
手
Wow, I really hate it.
うわ ぁ、めっちゃ嫌い
I don't understand that it's okay.
いいってことが分かんない
It tickles.
くすぐったいね
I have a smell fetish.
匂いフェチなんだよね
Give me a look.
ちょっと顔して
No way.
やだ
Do you want a hug?
ハグしたいの?
It tickles me.
くすぐったいって
tickles.
くすぐったい
You haven't done anything.
何もしてないね
tickles.
くすぐったい
Be still, be still.
じっとして、じっと
I can't do it.
できないって
Here.
ここで
Are you not doing anything?
何もしてないの?
Seriously.
まじ
Why don't you move because you don't cry?
なんで泣かないから動くの?
Can you see it reflected?
映ってるの見える?
Yeah.
うん
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
No way.
やだ
It doesn't work.
効かん
use?
使い?
what
何
Yo.
よ
Oh no.
や だ
Should it be this way?
こっちだったらいい?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
It's ticklish.
くすぐったいもん
Let's go out.
出ちゃう
tickles.
くすぐったい
Liar.
嘘つき
tickles.
くすぐったい
different?
違う?
tickles.
くすぐったい
Hold still for a moment.
ちょっとじっとしてよ
Big.
でかす
Will we be together?
一緒になる?
We're really together.
本当に一緒なんだ
Will we be together?
一緒になるの?
I have to cry a little.
ちょっと泣かないと
tickles.
くすぐったい
Hey.
ねえ
tickles.
くすぐったい
Then I'll stop here.
じゃあこっちやめる
That tickles me too.
そっちもくすぐったいって
tickles.
く すぐったい
It doesn't tickle, does it?
くすぐったくないでしょ
That's not true.
違うね
I'm hiding it.
隠してんだ
Can I see your pants?
パンツ見ていい?
No way.
やだ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Hiro
ひ ろ
I guess I should go.
い にいっちゃおうかな
I really don't like it.
本当にやだ
It's like good morning.
おはようしみたいな
Can I see it?
見ていいですか?
No.
だめ
why?
なんで?
I have to smell it.
匂いかけなきゃ
I don't like it.
嫌
So should I add it?
じゃあ足したらいい?
What do you mean by feet?
足ってどういうこと?
feet.
足
I really hate it.
めっちゃ嫌
You look amazing.
すごい顔してる
If you look like the soles of your feet are black,
足の裏黒くなってるぐらいの顔したら
Okay.
いい よ
Lie.
嘘つけ
TRUE?
本当?
I'm curious about that too.
そっちも気になるんだよね
I don't like it.
嫌だって
please.
お願い
I don't like it.
嫌だって
Really.
本当に
Really?
本当に?
What do you mean really?
本当にって言うのは?
Does that mean it's absolutely no good?
絶対ダメってこと?
Can I take a sneak peek later?
後で、こっそり見ていい?
Why do you make that face?
なんでそれ顔するの?
no.
いや
Isn't that embarrassing?
恥ずかしいってことでしょ?
I really don't like it anymore.
普通に本当にもう嫌
Why are you showing me your bottom like this?
こうやって下を見せてくれるのに?
That's fine, right?
そっちでいいってことでしょ?
Hands on the side.
手を横
Do this yourself, crow.
自分でこう、からす
through your hands.
手を通して
So that you can see inside.
中見えるように
Because I want to see it properly.
ちゃんと見たいから
beautiful.
きれい
Move your butt a little further forward.
もうちょっとお尻前にして
That's amazing.
すごいって
It hurts, right?
痛いでしょ?
it hurts?
痛い?
why?
なんで?
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛い
I'm being attacked, does it hurt?
やられてるけど痛いの?
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛い
Would you like a little more?
もうちょっといい?
Would it be nice if the nose had a different color?
鼻の色があったらいい?
Yeah.
うん
Look around here too.
この辺も眺めて
Hide it like that.
そのまんまでかくって
Because it's not in my mouth.
口に入ってないから
I've never done that before, Mouth.
したことないの、口
Yeah.
うん
Let's play.
遊ぼうせんの
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
it hurts?
痛い?
It's wet.
濡れてる
Complete
全
Isn't it moving?
然 動いてない?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Does it still hurt?
まだ痛い?
It doesn't hurt, right?
痛くないでしょ?
You don't hate it, right?
嫌じゃないでしょ?
dislike.
嫌い
difficult?
難しい?
It happened, right?
あったことでしょ?
Can I look at you from behind?
後ろ顔していい?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It looks wet.
濡れてるようだな
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
If it feels good.
もしも気持ちいい
I'll go again.
また行くぞ
I'll let it flow.
流すよ
It's okay if you let it flow.
流 せば大丈夫だから